Hello
Let me just let people know we are live stream. Oh
We got a post on Twitter, too
You just put this on Twitter
Happy YouTube live. This is happy you could live. I'm gonna be happy to that
Hello I
Don't want to distract these guys too much I newest employee started today. I
Think do you want to say hi to them did you do you want to say hi to the streamers you can wave?
Um
Patient. Yeah, so it were launched at this way shank. They'll be working on driver monitoring. We're gonna get dr
About it to 100% so you guys can't cheat anymore
Yeah, no phones. No sleeping. No
Looking at the nice side of the road keep your eyes on the road open pilots level 2
That's it okay be safe guys. Yeah. See you guys
Okay, um
So this is the 0.6. No, I'm not gonna go with Joe Rogan. It's not a band question, maybe so this is the 0.6
Stuff virtually crest nice to have you here. The biggest thing that we have is a new model
We've managed to ship a new model. We've managed to reduce the CPU on every line of open pilot is now open source our
Panta safety code is is misra compliant
Which means it's you know, the safety code is all it's written in like the same standard of see that every car manufacturer uses ah
Yeah, the hugging bug, ah, well, you know what if you show me a hugging bug we're gonna go for a drive
and
We'll see if there's a hugging bar right now. Oh
Well, you know what we'll grab viv and we'll take you by the data center I'll show you guys the data center
Oh, it's lunchtime. Oh, we're gonna miss lunch bed. We're gonna miss lunch. So we got to go. We already started the stream
Should we eat lunch and further YouTube live do his money lunch with us
We a health in it
It was gonna be hard to keep it steady
Oh
This is fantastic and I think there's lentil soup - wait, are you really eating lunch George you have to do a stream?
Say I just watched Georgie and I don't get to eat here I'll hold the phone I have to eat
You'll eat. I'm just doing a live stream. I just need to have a little bit
Okay. I don't know if I'm a great phone holder
Nice just like pretty girls doing these eating streams Oh George. Oh
Let us hear the mukbang voice, I don't know what that means
We have two mics it says that's good. I
Mean it grew is just it's just another step in making
Making the AI sentient, you know now remembers it holds grudges
Opening eyes dota player have one like 2048 unit. Yeah
Yeah, I mean they seem to remember a lot of things it was pretty cool you can just blind them sunlight
It's the sunlight blinds camera. They seem to just completely remember the road and keep going
Wait, why did people not believe will them was real?
See
also the gurus also use the speed of the car to
Determine the relevance of the lane lines implicitly consider eight
so now Lane lines
Need to have a life expectancy to be considered relevant for driving
Yes, so that's the solution to the exit problem that's why exits now are better without any hacks or you know weird if statements
Everyone knows George is favorite food is rice
There we can see George contaminating our food live on stream
Yeah, yeah and the streams canceled yeah, but we should have actually started on LT cuz the worse is switching
You think like naturally and so just turning it off
Yeah, we should turn off fuck yeah. All right guys we're taking you to LTE if this doesn't work
It's better than fireworks this is one gigabyte of storage
Did they say the quality's terrible they say they're bored and now we're back I think it was bad
You're really trying to hold it there, yeah because I get motion sickness when I watch videos that are like people
You know moving about terribly. Oh
No, we never found that stabilizer, I think it's upstairs, but I'm I have to climb the ladder which seems unsafe
The ladder is not safe
Should I get in the back and film would that be a better view?
Beautiful thing about cars like this is it's just like everything is done by hand. Nothing is automatic
So if there's an issue, you know, you can fix it
I mean
I'm not opposed
Insurance for other people not for us
Someone has already done to its car. Look at that
No, no too close natural, oh, yeah
All right guys welcome to
0.6
I'm gonna go to the highway. This is a happy stream. This is a happy stream only happy things
Yeah. Yeah, this reminds me of the road trip. This was like the angle the entire road trip. Yeah. Yeah. It's a great angle
So you see we have a we have a neon gold right here, which is available for sale at shop. Kamidana. Yeah, I
But so let's get them a highway and we'll cruise a little bit and then
I'd say I really want to find a street like the one when we drove to Connors house that night
Yeah, I got to test on that. Well, that's just a really nice Street to show off right? Yeah. Yeah models are a ton better
at making turns
At
Intersections just like all the things that are into highway driving. Yeah
I'm still gonna show you highway driving because I know how to go to the highway. That's right
I'm in San Diego. I feel like those streets are everywhere, you know
Hey, hey Scopus, do you see where we are?
you're gonna
Yeah, it's where are we guys fine is a good thing
I'm making sure that this is a decent stream of not too much bumpiness, but
We're engaged right now
We get a fuse for the stopped car
Well top cars come down the next in the top
Do you need a pedal for the 2020 Corolla? No, you know what?
We have no panel full stop and go this is the best car open pilot supports
Yeah, I'll hold the camera higher that's a good idea
You guys always talking about like turning off your lane changing I don't find a problem
Just like fighting it little I really like made like pulls me into the lane
You know the stupid video on a website and drive so slow it makes you think that open pilot is slow
You can set your speed so, you know
driving slow
It was me but it's you know, I had set it at my dead set it slow
I actually almost like had your voice in my head and I was like George is gonna be upset with how slow this car is
Driving it was like, oh well
You're very conservative driver George you're a very conservative driver
Going fast as a big problem a lot of accidents happen because people are going too fast and they lose control
Lotta accidents happen when people try to through sketchy shit like, oh I'm gonna cut across these
Someone just call it a slow roll and I love that
Guys here, we are difference. It's the
Confidence with which it dries
Part of this is the the incredible
That's alpha Corolla as well this by the way works on every 2020 Corolla so you can buy cheapest 2020 crow
I think you can actually get them from less than
$20,000 Wow
Raising the price system
Well now be a good time Maya because crisis only go up
Yeah presses when we go up folks. Should we try one of these rooms?
Yeah, see we'll see we'll drive is actually really fun beats
That's not the greatest of film on but we can try like yet towards PP. I
Don't have confidence while iana's on what should I do? Well, you should always pay attention. You're human. Yeah, well car
Look at that good steering angle sensor. Yeah, big Sara
How is this view for you guys?
Drive around the back. Is it gonna be new hardware upgrade to the Aeons?
What's on the windshield next the L cast cover
Yeah, it's really bumpy but we can do it right the road itself is very bumpy
Because we went with the videographer and Andrew. It's the car running all current hardware. It's yes all current hardware
Can great pan to be used to read and clear dtc codes with linux or other OS
We're still engaged we're just lowering
That's a stop guys
Always pay attention folks that's important
You should have got the phone gimble, you know what we had it we'll find it
What's upstairs? We did not almost crash
This is so meta because I'm also traveling with open pilot right now
If your trunk open file, you should not be yeah, you should be paying attention
Not watching YouTube. Alright, so guys like check it out. Like this turn would have been completely undoable with the old open pilots
Beautifully done
Wait, there's a car
So it's all that one, I don't know stop cars coming in the next version
So it resumes from a stop and now you're gonna see the legendary ability of 0.6 to go through intersections, oh, yeah
Yeah
Beautifully done
But yeah, you know, we're pushing where would you push engage time up?
So we should well, we don't even have a lane on this road. What's it gonna do?
What's doing actually? Yeah, it's doing a pretty good job
Turn still suck on Honda Civic Bosch due to limitations
They're better in the new model just a new model can
Roll if you're considering a new car they recommend the 2020 Corolla
From Longo Toyota if you're interested to
Stock car detection has always worked better for me to open pilot than Prius prime stock
You want to make it like perfect I want to have no questions about
Autopilot did not do this
Well at first and then some updates really approved it for autopilot and a Tesla can do what we can do it to
SDSU engaged or disengaged on its this is 80s sp2 car so it doesn't matter
Where they open pilot is doing
What trim is our Corolla highest trip
This is the poor man's autopilot well depends on the definition of poor man's
Things about it, they're better. There's some things about it that are worse
It's we emphasize like we're more conservative than Tesla our torque limits are as high we have driver monitoring
Here
Back to the office
No wonder that everyone's been quiet, can you run open pile on a PC mount in your car like yours?
this
is this is an Ellen for sale shop calm down AI for the low low price of
30-day return policy. That's right. You don't like it
But just go to our website comment on AI the top link just click check compatibility if you have a compatible car
Even if they're not that tech-savvy you'll probably be able to get it up on market. Yeah
lots of good YouTube videos
Good community on disco diversity Chris pushes or sex? I didn't see it. I saw he said a privately go. Yeah
Oh, the guy means a huge touchscreen like are like your old videos, oh no, no
No, is it dead system was terrible guys you mean that was the comma 0 you want to come at 0-0?
Given way mo bought a fleet of 65,000 Pacifica hybrids
More exciting virtually Chris video coming half hour almost done good. We're excited for Avicii. Yes
The squirrel has a power boom
All right, so we're gonna try driving by an exit. We're gonna see what happens
To stay in this lane
and we're gonna see if the
Legendary 0.6 nected fixes actually work. Someone wants to know where the graph is mounted. It's in here
with the cover on with the
National
Zoo can make your giraffe special - just like - Simon pliers
This isn't an exit. This is an urgent support for the 2016 Honda Accord with Honda sensing
Solidity on this turn
Yeah feels almost better than a human honestly
It's not we can go a little boy that is just as the new tour d'azyr never better
Yeah came a little bit out there because we're interns
You wanted you want to maximize?
Even just beer. So the old all odds you couldn't really stay in the right lane
because they could get on exits just
ask my
Does it do the same for left exits exits -
We've completely removed - all our left-hand drive people
We used to have something where it would hang to the left lane
That's been completely removed and the angle offset learner has been completely removed because the models are so much better
Someone's asked if there's any plans on flex, right? No. All right. So, let's see. We got a real exit here really likes it. Oh
No problem
Didn't even wiggle at all not even a question
Yeah, the old audible wiggle a little bit on the old the first autopilot
Did that too Tesla solved this at first with mapping which is kind of absurd now
They've solved it the same way we have
Mapping out every exit. Yes. That's our Tesla. Did it originally the ap1 marker?
Well, that's what Cruz um, supercruise does super cruisers mass average. Yeah
If you don't have
How do you write tests for such a thing as open pilot
Well, a lot of our tests the church is open source
We test run multiple deployments if transit has to be approval tests and hit all tests. I stole these terms of SpaceX they're real but
Moodle is hardware and out of the loop, which are alike
You can check out panda safety has very good
Testament up which are things that run on a computer and then middle
We have 13 Yuans in our office constantly running open pilot on historical data and making sure works
We have 112 they said the street cut out at one point, but I think it's back to being good
Okay, so this is an exit I take every day to get to the office and it's always a little schedule
Slowing down for turns was removed because it used the maps but now it's back to will and it back
Does open pilot roll slowly
Right now while you are using it
It doesn't learn while you're using it learns after you upload data to our data center
And then we have all of those computers crunch all your data looking to roll to this intersection. Look no
Been watching a loading open pilot for about five minutes
That's only because you're on davell if you're on release two you have to wait a little bit longer to get the updates
But you don't have to see that screen anymore. We shipped pre-built binding we ship pre-built binaries on released. Oh
Yeah
Can't wait to install this on my 79 Honda Accord sure
30 day policy
Don't buy it if you have an old car, where is your open pilot data strongest there's our data strong
Where's the donate button oh, I like that shop
Donate buy a hoodie bioody just buy a bunch of pandas buy a bunch of white pant.if. We have so many white pandas
Alright guys, that was it folks. Thank you for joining. Yeah. I hope you enjoyed it 0.6